{
    "id": "2bcc95fd88204ac2bcdd34f4c36f4b52",
    "title": "Few vs. Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She seemed the .............................. concerned.",
            "description": "The least concerned means not concerned at all. ",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "least",
                "fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9367d09caacf4923b2f60ce8a8869679"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got very ................................ friends.",
            "description": "Very few indicates a very small number. ",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "less",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d2ee4781a11a4755b5c552186488f5bf"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has got only ............................... friends.",
            "description": "Use a few after only.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "20600a6af0e74c6f9bf8f85048c1ced9"
        },
        {
            "question": ".............................. students attended the class today than yesterday.",
            "description": "A comparative form is required here. Use fewer with plural nouns and less with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Fewer",
                "less",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a859738c90d34dc4812f8b7dd5d92a46"
        },
        {
            "question": "I now have .............................. problems than I used to.",
            "description": "Use fewer with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "less"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd434b60ad4f440b9b3e935df1421f84"
        },
        {
            "question": "'She is upset with you.' 'I couldn't care .................................'",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74004bf306ed446fbcedaaad1088277b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He paid ................................ attention to what I was saying.",
            "description": "Little attention means hardly any attention. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "least",
                "fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5f9291169e6942548583843ab01fe25e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He finished the job with ................................ difficulty.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "716022bf6cc44af1ba72ad33fbb3668c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The task was ............................... difficult than I thought.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little. A comparative word is required before than. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c36c3ee5fc0d412799f962f52f710864"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was the .................................... popular among them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2c7251adce7a4c4fb1b3384255342068"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ................................ concern for name or fame.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ebb1158818846a192ee28ba6536307d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know very .................................... people in this town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "fewer",
                "fewest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb92f704c6b04b12bc8f258aa7ec5c07"
        }
    ]
}